Contact

courtneybrady9@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/courtney-brady-naftaly-cmsrn-864905ba (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Patient Advocacy
Elder Care
Quality Patient Care

Languages

English

Certifications

MSNCB

Narcan/Opiod Overdose Certification SALT Mass Casualty Triage Training ACLS/AED Diabetes Champion

Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau International Nursing Honor Society

Deans List

Magna Cum Laude

Recognition Award

State of NY Triple C Award for "Commitment, Character, and Courage" to change the community for the better.

Courtney Brady-Naftaly, CMSRN

Assistant Nurse Manager at Northwell Health Greater New York City Area

Summary

I am a positive, energetic, and passionate RN that happens to be a huge supporter of self-growth. I not only believe that every moment we experience is an opportunity for learning and improvement, but it excites me. I have an insatiable hunger to improve on my education and better myself. This helps me in my journey as an RN because I am always ready and willing to learn, no matter who is the teacher or what their level of education is. I am currently the Co Chair for the Collaborative Care Council, and sit in the Chief Nursing Officers cabinet meetings monthly to learn more about issues we face as a hospital, and to initiate change to solve those issues. I am a tremendous patient advocate, and only put forth the highest quality care for my patients as well as staff. My positive and up-beat attitude helps promote a happy and exciting work environment as well as an open line of communication for anyone who needs help. I take my work extremely serious, and put 110% in every thing I do. I am a big believer in checking, re-checking, and checking again! In a profession where a mistake could be extremely detrimental to someones health, I ensure that I minimize the margin of error as much as I possibly can. I am currently an Assistant Nurse Manager with experience in treating Med-Surg, Telemetry, Stroke, Oncology, and Pulmonary patients. I have earned the title as a Diabetes Champion, where I am a resource for my unit as well as other units in the hospital for any questions or help in educating patients newly diagnosed with diabetes! I love teaching and helping patients as well as fellow nurses, and was honored to have received the national Mentorship Award from Northwell Health. I am truly so lucky to be a nurse and can not wait to see what my future holds. Below is a research paper I did while externing at Memorial Sloan Kettering to help decrease complications and increase patient outcomes while people are receiving cancer treatments!

Experience

Northwell Health

4 years 9 months

Assistant Nurse Manager

June 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Long island Jewish Medical Center

Telemetry

Registered Nurse

October 2016 - Present (3 years 10 months)

Greater New York City Area

3 North, part of the telemetry division of Northwell Health

Co-Chair of Collaborative Care Council

I am a Diabetes champion for our unit and as a recourse for other units.

Sit on the Chief Nursing Officers cabinet meetings.

Received patients from CTICU/CCU/ICU

Received patients after cardiac procedures

Clinical ladder 1

Registered Nurse

November 2015 - October 2016 (1 year)

Long Island Jewish Hospital New Hyde Park

5 South/Respiratory Care Unit/Advanced Illness/Care Model

Received patients from the Medical ICU

Cared for adult patients that were ventilator dependent

Assessed and completed patient care for tracheostomies

Nursing care for patients on continuous pulse oximetry

Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center

Preceptor/Capstone

April 2015 - May 2015 (2 months)

Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center, NY

Completed 165 hours following an RN preceptor

Assessed, Planned, Implemented, and Evaluated care for oncology patients

Collaborated with all members of the Health Care Team

Communicated with families regarding patients progression and status

Hung IV medications, gave subcutaneous injections, and administered oral medications

Ambulated patients first day post operation

Mayan Families

Medical Mission

January 2015 - January 2015 (1 month)

Completed height and weight assessments

Promoted secondary prevention by administering vision and dental screenings to severely impoverished and malnourished children.

Donated, built, and installed safer stoves throughout homes in the indigenous mountain villages around Panajachel.

Prepared and served meals to malnourished children and elderly Made home visits to severely deprived communities

National Multiple Sclerosis Society
Assistant Programs Director/Community Fellows Program
May 2013 - August 2013 (4 months)

Worked as part of the Adelphi University Community Fellowship Program Helped organize and facilitate Newly Diagnosed Night and provided education to members

Gave emotional support to any members that were diagnosed with Multiple Sclerosis

Visited members at their homes to help assist with daily activities and chores

Education

Adelphi University

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2015)